{"updatedAt": 1593163778450, "questionSet": [{"attempts": [], "question": "-LBggsND2ZVE5mPNWqV0"}, {"attempts": [], "question": "-LBghPZamp3QxHT0fvo6"}, {"attempts": [], "question": "-LBggyHYTFK_GwP-PtM-"}, {"attempts": [], "question": "-LBghGSN-i3Z8esMdvrP"}, {"attempts": [], "question": "-LBghV-ckevuExGqIwIJ"}, {"attempts": [], "question": "-LBghaF2MnjXn5YS7pqL"}, {"attempts": [], "question": "-LBgi0_MD5bltIgGI_uM"}, {"attempts": [], "question": "-LBghB0vlzuEEd0pUx9c"}, {"attempts": [], "question": "-LBghglx86fdHMe_py_w"}, {"attempts": [], "question": "-LBgh5aEf3NQeV_9vuIS"}], "answeredQuestions": [{"attempts": [{"response": {"id": 6461773, "key": "6461773", "text": "The government meets to discuss the new law.", "count": 57255, "optimal": true, "feedback": "<p>That's a strong sentence!</p>", "child_count": 28704, "question_uid": "-LBggsND2ZVE5mPNWqV0", "conceptResults": {"kztNiLIidtfBZF6qbgfRKw": {"correct": true, "conceptUID": "kztNiLIidtfBZF6qbgfRKw"}}, "concept_results": [{"correct": false, "conceptUID": "kztNiLIidtfBZF6qbgfRKw"}], "first_attempt_count": 13836}}], "question": "-LBggsND2ZVE5mPNWqV0"}, {"attempts": [{"response": {"id": 6461317, "key": "6461317", "text": "The students are studying for the exam.", "count": 57168, "optimal": true, "feedback": "<p>That's a strong sentence!</p>", "child_count": 9977, "question_uid": "-LBghPZamp3QxHT0fvo6", "conceptResults": {"Tlhrx6Igxn6cR_SD1U5efA": {"correct": true, "conceptUID": "Tlhrx6Igxn6cR_SD1U5efA"}}, "concept_results": [{"correct": false, "conceptUID": "Tlhrx6Igxn6cR_SD1U5efA"}], "first_attempt_count": 19066}}], "question": "-LBghPZamp3QxHT0fvo6"}, {"attempts": [{"response": {"id": 6461231, "key": "6461231", "text": "The company has 25 workers.", "count": 56912, "optimal": true, "feedback": "<p>That's a strong sentence!</p>", "child_count": 10227, "question_uid": "-LBggyHYTFK_GwP-PtM-", "conceptResults": {"kztNiLIidtfBZF6qbgfRKw": {"correct": true, "conceptUID": "kztNiLIidtfBZF6qbgfRKw"}}, "concept_results": [{"correct": false, "conceptUID": "kztNiLIidtfBZF6qbgfRKw"}], "first_attempt_count": 18601}}], "question": "-LBggyHYTFK_GwP-PtM-"}, {"attempts": [{"response": {"text": "The flock of birds fly over the town.", "count": 1, "author": "Incorrect Sequence Hint", "feedback": "<p>Revise your work. <em>Fly</em> is used with more than one bird. Change the action word so it works with <strong>one group</strong> of birds.</p>", "parent_id": 6461288, "question_uid": "-LBghGSN-i3Z8esMdvrP", "concept_results": {"kztNiLIidtfBZF6qbgfRKw": {"key": "kztNiLIidtfBZF6qbgfRKw", "name": "Verbs | Subject Verb Agreement | Collective Nouns", "correct": false, "conceptUID": "kztNiLIidtfBZF6qbgfRKw"}}}}, {"response": {"id": 6461288, "key": "6461288", "text": "The flock of birds flies over the town.", "count": 55046, "optimal": true, "feedback": "<p>That's a strong sentence!</p>", "child_count": 45001, "question_uid": "-LBghGSN-i3Z8esMdvrP", "conceptResults": {"kztNiLIidtfBZF6qbgfRKw": {"correct": true, "conceptUID": "kztNiLIidtfBZF6qbgfRKw"}}, "concept_results": [{"correct": false, "conceptUID": "kztNiLIidtfBZF6qbgfRKw"}], "first_attempt_count": 7644}}], "question": "-LBghGSN-i3Z8esMdvrP"}, {"attempts": [{"response": {"id": 6461329, "key": "6461329", "text": "The sailboat moves quickly in the strong wind.", "count": 55764, "optimal": true, "feedback": "<p>That's a strong sentence!</p>", "child_count": 10769, "question_uid": "-LBghV-ckevuExGqIwIJ", "conceptResults": {"Tlhrx6Igxn6cR_SD1U5efA": {"correct": true, "conceptUID": "Tlhrx6Igxn6cR_SD1U5efA"}}, "concept_results": [{"correct": false, "conceptUID": "Tlhrx6Igxn6cR_SD1U5efA"}], "first_attempt_count": 18082}}], "question": "-LBghV-ckevuExGqIwIJ"}, {"attempts": [{"response": {"id": 6461348, "key": "6461348", "text": "My friend has a yellow scooter.", "count": 55842, "optimal": true, "feedback": "<p>That's a strong sentence!</p>", "child_count": 7050, "question_uid": "-LBghaF2MnjXn5YS7pqL", "conceptResults": {"Tlhrx6Igxn6cR_SD1U5efA": {"correct": true, "conceptUID": "Tlhrx6Igxn6cR_SD1U5efA"}}, "concept_results": [{"correct": false, "conceptUID": "Tlhrx6Igxn6cR_SD1U5efA"}], "first_attempt_count": 19326}}], "question": "-LBghaF2MnjXn5YS7pqL"}, {"attempts": [{"response": {"id": 6461406, "key": "6461406", "text": "The flowers in the garden are growing quickly.", "count": 55205, "optimal": true, "feedback": "<p>That's a strong sentence!</p>", "child_count": 11351, "question_uid": "-LBgi0_MD5bltIgGI_uM", "conceptResults": {"Tlhrx6Igxn6cR_SD1U5efA": {"correct": true, "conceptUID": "Tlhrx6Igxn6cR_SD1U5efA"}}, "concept_results": [{"correct": false, "conceptUID": "Tlhrx6Igxn6cR_SD1U5efA"}], "first_attempt_count": 17689}}], "question": "-LBgi0_MD5bltIgGI_uM"}, {"attempts": [{"response": {"id": 6461274, "key": "6461274", "text": "The group waits to get on the roller coaster.", "count": 55187, "optimal": true, "feedback": "<p>That&#x27;s a strong sentence!</p>", "child_count": 10370, "question_uid": "-LBghB0vlzuEEd0pUx9c", "conceptResults": {"kztNiLIidtfBZF6qbgfRKw": {"correct": true, "conceptUID": "kztNiLIidtfBZF6qbgfRKw"}}, "concept_results": [{"correct": false, "conceptUID": "kztNiLIidtfBZF6qbgfRKw"}], "first_attempt_count": 17784}}], "question": "-LBghB0vlzuEEd0pUx9c"}, {"attempts": [{"response": {"id": 6461362, "key": "6461362", "text": "The city lights are very bright.", "count": 55029, "optimal": true, "feedback": "<p>That's a strong sentence!</p>", "child_count": 7131, "question_uid": "-LBghglx86fdHMe_py_w", "conceptResults": {"Tlhrx6Igxn6cR_SD1U5efA": {"correct": true, "conceptUID": "Tlhrx6Igxn6cR_SD1U5efA"}}, "concept_results": [{"correct": false, "conceptUID": "Tlhrx6Igxn6cR_SD1U5efA"}], "first_attempt_count": 19033}}], "question": "-LBghglx86fdHMe_py_w"}, {"attempts": [{"response": {"id": 6461257, "key": "6461257", "text": "A couple is holding hands at the bus stop.", "count": 54081, "optimal": true, "feedback": "<p>That's a strong sentence!</p>", "child_count": 31347, "question_uid": "-LBgh5aEf3NQeV_9vuIS", "conceptResults": {"kztNiLIidtfBZF6qbgfRKw": {"correct": true, "conceptUID": "kztNiLIidtfBZF6qbgfRKw"}}, "concept_results": [{"correct": false, "conceptUID": "kztNiLIidtfBZF6qbgfRKw"}], "first_attempt_count": 10668}}], "question": "-LBgh5aEf3NQeV_9vuIS"}], "unansweredQuestions": []}
